Here's what I found out.
The receptionist is her cousin.
Did she give it to you?
Golda's number?
No.
You've been staring at me
since I sat down.
- Who are you?
- That's a former cop, Boss!
A terror during drug busts
but turns out he's a cop killer.
Ramon Orbos, the cop
they say I killed...
do you know him?
You know what my mother
always used to say?
Don't talk to strangers.
There she is.
Let's go.
Wait, the bag's gone.
She left it inside.
Golda is coming from there,
right?
- But when?
- We don't know yet,
but she will show up.
She's here.
If my instinct is correct,
that bag contains the money,
and Golda will come to get it.
That is how she collects.
How did you find me?
No one knows you're here.
I'm Miguel Delgado's daughter.
Golda, please,
have mercy on my father!
You know what happened
to Parak, right?
I don't want to end up like him!
Don't come near me!
Stop following me!
She can't escape!
It'll be even harder
to find Golda now.
Because you showed yourself.
The woman who ruined my family
was right in front of me.
Was I supposed to do nothing?
We all know that.
You're not using your brain.
Sorry, okay?
I'm not a robot like you.
Fine, I'll have
the shipment prepared.
You seem happy.
I think my work here is done.
The smear campaign
against Delgado and Parak
is solidly in place.
Everyone hates them.
Look at this.
“Make them suffer.”
“Torture them.”
“Feed them to the ants
and to the crocodiles
like them.”
Post a comment.
Say it's done.
The news is spreading so fast,
and the damage keeps on growing.
I love social media
and its netizens.
But we still haven't fixed
one problem.
Golda is also too slippery.
It's supposed
to be Parak's problem.
That cop was reckless.
He's already dead but he left us
a problem to deal with.
Loloy.
Any information about Golda?
None yet, Boss.
I asked all our dealers
like her.
No one knows where she is.
Find her before she starts
to make a mess.
Now!
Let's go.
Still thinking about Golda?
I just don't know
what I'm doing wrong anymore.
I feel like everything's
falling apart.
The video...
Godfather Diego...
and now, Golda.
She was the only one
who could help me,
and now she's gone too.
I just want to help dad.
But whatever I do,
I always messed it up.
You know,
maybe Andrew is right.
I'm the reason why everything
is falling apart.
No.
You're not.
Golda, you're guilty, right?
Because I met Major Delgado.
He's a good man.
That's why I know
you feel guilty
about all the things
you did to him.
Elai, Kyle.
Boss?
Yes, Boss?
Look for this.
What is it?
It will lead us to Golda.
She's a valuable informant.
We have to find her.
Okay.
- Yes, Boss.
- Let's go.
You're going out?
We are going out.
Get dressed.
Where are we going?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
I'm coming too.
Where to?
We can still track down, Golda.
Let's go.
How?
I told you I don't know
where she is.
Dewi, please.
We're sure you still have
contact with Golda.
We just need
to talk to her, please.
Sorry, I don't want to break
Golda's trust in me.
You, Oppa.
You used me.
You made me a fool.
I'm sorry.
Look, we just need to talk
to Golda.
So...
please tell me.
What can I do
to make it up to you?
Don't do that.
I'm weak when it comes to that.
Hello, Peter?
Joey...
The syndicate is here,
they're about to enter the spa.
What?
Go, go!
Excuse me.
Where's Golda?
She's not here!
You won't tell us?
Where is she?
Say it now!
They went in there.
They're coming.
Okay, okay.
There they are.
Go! Go!
Stop!
Jin Ho?
What are you waiting for?
Shoot him!
- Call the police!
- I am!
Call the police!
We have to go!
Hurry! Let's go!
Wait!
Okay!
Come on, hurry!
- You go, first!
- Come on, hurry!
Go! Go!
- It's locked!
- Yes, over the gate.
Just climb the gate.
Hey, this way! This way!
We are going to die!
Who are they?
Do not look! Hide!
Don't scold us!
It's not our fault!
We'll get out of here!
Just hide!
Joey, where are you?
There are so many gunshots,
are you okay?
Peter...
we went out the back.
Golda's cousin is with us.
I see a road here at the back.
Go here.
Okay, I'll circle around.
Okay, okay.
Jin Ho, Peter is coming!
Okay, go, Joey.
Take care, I'll cover you.
How about you?
Don't worry, I'm okay.
I'll meet you
at the boarding house, promise.
Okay.
On the count of three,
you run, okay?
Okay.
One...
Two...
Three! You run!
Joey, let's go!
Wait.
Jin Ho!
Go!
Joey, come on, let's go!
Let's move ahead!
Get out of here!
- Joey, we have to go first!
- Joey!
Let's leave them!
I'll verify that part, okay?
Just wait.
Boss...
I got something.
What is it?
Batikang Ganda?
Yup.
It's a women's clothing
and lifestyle store.
They only have one branch.
Their products are handmade,
and their fabrics are sourced
from abroad.
Where's the store located?
Wait, I'll check.
Where are they now?
Looks like they managed
to escape, Boss.
It's impossible for them
to get that far that fast.
Let's move.
Let's go, Bro!
Here.
Pass me a glass, Joey.
You know, I already checked.
No one's following us,
we're safe.
Good thing Jin Ho blocked
the ones chasing you.
It was effective.
Good thing that Korean is brave
even if he's a bit
of a trickster.
It's really good you came
with us, Dewi.
At least, you weren't caught
by the ones chasing us earlier.
Exactly,
that's what I was thinking.
If not, I'd probably be dead.
Thank you, really.
I wonder where Jin Ho is.
He's still not answering.
Joey, you'll just put him
in more danger
if you keep calling.
That's enough.
I'm worried, he got shot.
Come on, that's probably just
like an ant bite to him.
Isn't he Korean intelligence?
That means he's used to combat.
- Don't worry.
- But, still...
And you know what?
He stayed behind
just to make sure Dewi and I
got away safely.
He's still not answering,
where could he be?
- Jin Ho!
- Oppa!
We were worried about you!
I'm okay.
You're bleeding.
It's nothing.
There is more important
things to do.
No, let's go to the hospital.
- You have to get checked.
- No, no, no.
I'm really okay.
No worries.
So...
are you ready to tell us...
where Golda is?
Dewi's asleep,
she got exhausted.
Oh, what's that?
What's that?
A tetanus shot.
I always bring one,
just in case,
for situation like this.
You know, here in our country...
we just use soap for tetanus.
Laundry bar soap.
A shot? That's over the top.
Let me help you.
I'll do it.
Let me do it.
What?
Let me see.
It's not even that deep.
You have nothing
to worry about.
Why? Does it hurt?
- It hurts, right?
- Hey.
It's not even that deep, see?
Get off of me, man.
You know what,
let's just talk about Golda.
Joey!
What are you doing here?
Oh, what?
Do you have a wound too?
Wait, what happened there?
Long story.
- We went...
- Later, later.
I have something
more important to say.
I know where we can find Golda.
We already know too.
- In Amoroso.
How did you find out?
From the logo on Golda's shirt
when we went to see her.
There's only one store
with that logo, Joey.
It's in Amoroso.
What about you?
How did you find out?
From Dewi, Golda's cousin.
She finally admitted it.
Well, I guess, it's nice.
All I knew was the store,
but I didn't know the exact
location.
At least, her cousin told you
where Golda really is.
Not exactly where.
Of course, Golda's scared
of being followed.
What's important is we know
she goes home to Amoroso.
I guess...
we're going to Amoroso.
We got nothing
from the spa, Boss.
The therapists didn't know
anything.
The manager,
who's Golda's cousin,
we almost caught her.
Almost?
She got away, Ma'am.
The Korean helped her
the one we had
a run-in with before.
What does he have to do
with Golda?
Not Golda, you.
He definitely has an idea
about our organization.
He's watching our every move.
He'll use anyone...
just to get closer to you.
Looks like he wants to sabotage
everything we're doing.
Exactly.
You won't even realize it...
you're already walking
straight towards him.
That bastard.
He really won't stop.
Fine.
I'll turn the heat up
and burn his whole game down.
Wait, wait, wait.
What? All of us are going?
Even you, Joey?
Even him?
Are you sure you trust him?
And why wouldn't she?
I'm part of finding Golda.
Wait, who said the two of you
are coming?
I don't trust you.
I only trust Joey.
So when I said “we,”
I meant just the two of us.
You're not invited.
You're pretty bossy.
Joey's the only one
who gets to decide, not you.
I'm Joey's bodyguard,
and she's not going anywhere
without me.
Same!
I'm her plus-one.
I'm her best friend.
You know,
if I'm going to Amoroso,
of course, I'd ask for help...
and the three of you are exactly
who I'd think to bring.
See? There you go.
But if you're all going
to keep fighting,
then I'll just go alone.
We might mess this up
if you keep acting like that.
So what?
Are you still going to argue?
If it's just to find Golda,
fine.
Peter?
Okay, fine, Peter.
All right.
Jin Ho.
Fine.
Okay, good.
So we're all going, okay?
Where are you going?
I'll sit there, I'll sit there.
I'll sit here.
Wait, are we really going
to fight over the seat too?
Yes, even the seat.
Why?
Fine, sit there.
Joey and I will sit at the back.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'll just sit at the back.
It's spacious.
Smells nice, I'll stay here.
Stay there.
Okay?
Andrew...
Yes?
I just wanted to thank you
for coming to tell me
where Golda was.
But you didn't need it.
Right?
Actually, you know what?
You're really good.
I admire you.
You managed to do that
on your own.
You found Golda.
Not really, Jin Ho and Peter
were with me.
But...
I really appreciate that...
even after the not-so-nice
things I said to you,
you still wanted to help me.
So thank you, Andrew.
What are you doing back there?
Let's go!
Come on. Let's go.
I don't want to get complacent,
especially since others are also
looking for Golda.
- Golda.
- Godfather!
When was the last time
you spoke to Braganza?
Our clients are with him now.
Miss, may I ask something?
Do you know someone named
Golda Briones?
I think that's Golda.
Golda!
That's Golda's car.
Let's just follow it.
I'm sure it'll lead us to her.
My friend replied already
about the plate number
you asked us to check.
It's registered
to Vincente Alcala.
Do you know the one
they call Godfather?
Godfather?
She went into hiding
under another syndicate.
Braganza has a target
here in Luzon.
There's going to be a party
at Godfather's place.
Guess who got an invite.
Then we have no other choice
but to infiltrate
that Godfather's villa.